http://www.realclimate.org/index.php/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Filed under:
— gavin @ 7 December 2018
Who we are
Our website address is: http://www.realclimate.org. We are a collection of climate scientists who blog about climate science and related issues.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we save the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. The IP address/browser user agent/email information is not used for any other purpose and not supplied to any third party.
Contact forms
The contact form saves an email address for notification of new posts or a digest. The emails are not used for any other purpose and are not provided to anyone else.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, tweets, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
How we protect your data
The blog database is password protected and backed-up daily to a secure site.
Comments Off on Privacy Policy.
Comments are closed.
New studies confirm weakening of the Gulf Stream circulation (AMOC): Victor
Unforced Variations: Nov 2020: Ed Addis
Unforced Variations: Nov 2020: Alastair B. McDonald
Unforced Variations: Oct 2020: James McDonald
New studies confirm weakening of the Gulf Stream circulation (AMOC): Nemo
Myth vs. Fact Regarding the “Hockey Stick”
On attribution
On mismatches between models and observations
On Sensitivity (Part I)
Tropical Glacier Retreat
Water Vapour: feedback or forcing?
Effets de Terre (FR)
PrimaKlima (DE)
What on Earth Comic Strip (Archive)
What's up with that Watts
World View of Glob.Warm.
Yale Climate Media Forum
Science Links
AIP:Discovery of Glob. Warm.
Columbia Earth Inst.
Penn State Inst. Env.
(availability denoted by flag icons)
Email Notification
Enter your e-mail address to receive notifications when there are new posts.
